Heiko Oberman Papers 1949-2016 (bulk 1985-2001)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Teaching materials, circa 1950-1998; Series III
  - Medieval Intellectual History, Harvard and U of A History 407, 1988, 1989, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - History 407/507B Medieval Intellectual History, 1990, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - History 195A: Debates with Historians, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - History 596F: Early Modern Europe, Doctoral Seminar, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - History 396H: Regents undergrad honors, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - History 101: Western Civilization, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - History 101, Jon’s Notes Inc., 1995, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - History 407/507B: Medieval Intellectual History, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Organization files, 1977-2004; Series IV
  Project files and correspondence related to work on committees, editorial and executive boards for various organizations. Organized alphabetically.
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1990-2001 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - American Cusanus Society, 1997-2001 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - American Historical Association, 1993-1996 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - American Philosophical Society, 1991-2001 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Archive for Reformation History, 1994-2000 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Aretê Encyclopedia, Editorial Board, Theology, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Arizona Center for Medieval and Renaissance Studies, advisory board, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - British Academy, 1988-2001 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Calvin Studies Society, 1990-2001 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Center for the Study of World History, University of Amsterdam, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Church History Society of South Africa, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Classics of Western Spirituality, Editorial Committee, 1977-1988 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Collected Works of Erasmus, Advisory Committee, University of Toronto, 1979-1993 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Constantijn Huygens Instituut (CHI), evaluation, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - De Calvin A. Bayle (collection), Comité de Patronage, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Disputatio journal, advisory board, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Duke University, Arts and Sciences Visiting Committee, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - English series, Reformation, Kluwer Academic Publishers, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, Western Center Executive Council meetings, 1989, 1990, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Grolier Multimedia Encyclopedia, Advisory Board, 1987-2004 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Heineken Prize for History, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - History of Antisemitism project, American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Herausgabe der Worke Martin Luthur, WA-AWA, 1986-1988 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Journal of Church History, 1997-2001 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Journal of Ecclesiastical History, Editorial Advisory Board, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Ker ken Theologie, Advisory Board, 1988-1992 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - KNOW, Royal Netherlands Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1991-1994 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Library of Classical Protestant Theological Texts, Advisory Board, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Meeter Center, board meetings, 1991-1994 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Meeter Center, board meetings, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Meeter Center, board meetings, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Medieval Academy of America, 1989-1998 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Medieval Institute (Division Gathering), Kalamazoo, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - New Wyclif Society Editorial Board, Univ. of Ottawa, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Reformation and Renaissance Review, Editorial Board, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Renaissance Society of America, 1989-1996 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Rudolf Agricola Instituut, advisory board, 1994-1996 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Sixteenth Century Studies Conference, business meetings, 1990-1998 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Stichting ter Bevordering van de Kennis van de Reformatie, 1988-1995 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Studi e Testi per la Storia Religiosa del Cinquecento, series, Scientific Committee, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Studies in Reformation Theology and History, Princeton Theological Seminary, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Studies in Spirituality (series), Titus Brandsma Instituut, 1990, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Studies in the Reformation, Editorial Board, Ohio University, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Society for Reformation Research, 1985, 1986, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Secor Dabar, 1992, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Tyndale Advisory Committee, University of Tübingen, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - University of Groningan, advisory board, 1995-2001 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Western Center, American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1989-1993 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Zeitschrift für Kirchengeschichte, Editorial Board, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Project Files, 1958-2008; Series V
  - Book and Article Reviews, 1958-2001; Subseries 1
    Correspondence, manuscripts and publications related to reviews of academic works for colleagues and publishers.
    - Reviews, pending, 1984-2000 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Reviews, declined requests, 1984-2004 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Reviews, 1958-1984 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Reviews, completed with final copy attached, 1985-1987 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Review of “Historical Worlds, Literary History”, by Brian Stock, circa 1987 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Review requests, Nederlands Thjeologisch Tijdschrift (NTT), 1985-1990 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Reviews, 1986-1993 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Reviews, completed with final copy attached, 1988-1990 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Reviews, books, outstanding, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Reviews, completed with final copy attached, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Reviews, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Reviews, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Reviews, completed, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Reviews, completed, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Reviews of “Martin Luther: The Christian between God and Death”, by Richard Marius, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Review of “La Formazione Storica Della Alterita”, 1999-2001 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Reviews completed, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Book Purchases and Inventory, 1981-1998; Subseries 2
    Files related to Oberman’s personal library and management of his own publications. Includes: publication inventories, sales, distribution lists, financial documents, invoices and correspondence with publishers and book dealers.
    - Book stocks (copies of HAO’s publications), 1991-1998 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Offprints, distribution of HAO publications, 1986-1997 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Book sales, HAO publications, 1990-1998 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Calvin, distribution lists, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Luther, distribution and sales, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Distribution lists, other HAO publications, 1981-1988, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Books ordered from publishers, 1988-1992 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Books ordered from publishers (continued), 1988-1992 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Books received from publishers, 1985-1990 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Books received from publishers (continued), 1985-1990 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Books received from publishers (continued), 1985-1990 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Publishers invoices, old book orders, 1985-1988 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Manuscripts and Project Files, 1970-2008; Subseries 3
    Project files, drafts (bulk), and correspondence for Oberman’s major academic works including publications, manuscripts for lectures, research materials, work with publishers and other collaborative works. Organized chronologically.
    - Luther and Thomas, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Luther and Zwingli, Madison, WI, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Toward Recovery of Historical Calvin: Redrawing the Map of Reformation in Europe, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Mysticism, German lecture notes, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Erasmus, NRC and Robert Holkot, notes, bibliography, Quodlibetal questions, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Jews, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Initia Calvini: Die Entwicklung Calvins als Reformator, German translation, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Clippings, 1970-2000 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - KG II, notes and research materials, German, circa 1975 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - KG II, SS73, notebook, German, circa 1975 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - KG II, notes and research materials, German, circa 1975 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Geschichte Der Mystik, notes, German, circa 1975 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Kreuzwege der Geistesgischichte, notes, German, circa 1975 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Theologie Luthers, notes, German, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Warden und Wertung der Reformation, reviews, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Warden und Wertung der Reformation, thank you letters and reviews, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Sternstunden Der Christenheit, sections 3-8, German, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Sternstunden Der Christenheit, sections 4-6, German, circa 1978 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Bürgerliche Geschichtsschreibung, notes and drafts, 1978, undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - KG III, Mystik, notes, 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Civitas Dei, Corpus Christi, Congregatio Fidelium, possibly unpublished, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Contracts, publishers, 1985-2001 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Fortune, Faith and Females, St. Augustine, University of Arizona, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - The Stubborn Jews, English and German, 1986-1988 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Teufelsdreck, translation, Chicago, 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Central Policy Committee for Catholic Inst. Of Theological Education, Utrecht, 1986-1988 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Calvin Book #1, The Heritage of Calvin, Kuyper Lectures, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Calvin’s Legacy, draft, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Calvin (Major), English version, 1991-1996 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Calvin’s Legacy: Its Greatness and Limitations, correspondence, 1987-1992 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Calvin’s Legacy: Its Greatness and Limitations, correspondence, 1994-2008 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Requests for articles, Trappman, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Luther, WS, notes, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Luther, typed notes, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Luther: Man Between God and the Devil, Yale University Press, 1985-1989 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Luther: Man Between God and the Devil, Yale University Press, 1989-1991 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Luther: Man Between God and the Devil, Yale University Press (continued), 1989-1991 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Luther: Man Between God and the Devil, extension for English edition, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Luther: Man Between God and the Devil, index, style sheet, captions, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Luther: Man Between God and the Devil, abbreviation and notes, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Luther: Man Between God and the Devil, review draft, pp. 17-250, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Luther: Man Between God and the Devil, reviewed draft, pp. 251-512, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Luther: Man Between God and the Devil, reviewed draft, pp. 194-444, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Luther: Man Between God and the Devil, illustrations, Yale University Press, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Luther: Man Between God and the Devil, illustrations, Yale University Press, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Luther: Man Between God and the Devil, illustrations, Yale University Press (continued), 1989 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Luther: Man Between God and the Devil, illustrations- positive transparencies, Yale University Press, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Luther: Man Between God and the Devil, illustrations- color portrait of Luther, Yale University Press, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Luther: Man Between God and the Devil, illustrations taken out, Yale University Press, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Luther: Man Between God and the Devil, translation by Eileen Walliser-Schwarzbart, heavily corrected by HAO, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Luther: Man Between God and the Devil, translation by Eileen Walliser-Schwarzbart, heavily corrected by HAO (continued), 1989 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Review of Michael Joyce’s book on Luther, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Review of Michael Joyce’s book on Luther (continued), 1987 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - HAO Resumes and bibliographies, 1991-1996, undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Die Gelehrten die Verkehrten, multiple versions, 1987-1989 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Pater Trapp, Festschrift, 1987-1991 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Popular Response to Learned Culture, Harvard, 1987, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Stubborn Jews, Italian, Caruci (Veronese), 1988 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Stubborn Jews, Leo Baeck Institute, 1988-1990 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Martin Anton Schmidt, Festschrift, 1988-1990 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Initia Calvini: The Matrix of Calvin’s Reformation, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Initia Calvini: The Matrix of Calvin’s Reformation, 1990-1992 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - The Discovery of Hebrew and the Discrimination of Jews, Gerald Strauss Festschrift, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Gottfried W. Locher, Festschrift, 1990-1993 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Bibliotheca dissidentium, André Séguenny, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Martin Brecht, Festschrift, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Anticlericalism volume, preface, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Europa Afflicta: The Reformation of the Refugees, 1991-1993 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - The Development of Anti-Semitism from the Middle Ages to Early Modern Times, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - The Pursuit of Happiness, Trinkaus Festschrift (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Johannes Reuchlin: From Jewish Subjugation to Liberation (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Dohna Festschrift, Darmstadt, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Te Bolsec Controversy, foreward, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - The Trevail of Tolerance, Cambridge, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - East of Eden, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Gansfort, Reuchlin and the ‘Obscure Men’, Meuthen Festschrift, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Hidden Treasures: Library Holdings Changing History, Tucson Literary Club, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Rauchlin and the Jews: Obstacles on the Path to Emancipation, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Nederman volume, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Luthur Today, German, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Calvin and Farel, Reformation and Renaissance Review, Paul Ayris, 1996-1999 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - John Bossy Festschrift, University of York, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - The Devil and the Devious Historian, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Rediscovered books, list, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Hus and Luther, George Williams Festschrift, English translation, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Toward Recovery of Historical Calvin, Calvin Congress, Seoul, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Kaspar Elm Festschrift, Franz Felten, 1998-1999 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Zur Mühlen Festschrift, 1998-2000 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Apocalype, Ben Loeterman, PBS project, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Intro, Reformations of Europe, Routledge, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Froben Augustine Edition, Plowright/Way, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Der Bilderstreit im Zeitalter der Reformation, Bern, incomplete, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - The Two Reformations, drafts, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - The Two Reformations, terms and preface, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - The Two Reformations, draft chapter 5: The Aggressive Reformation, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - The Two Reformations, correspondence, HAO and family, colleagues, publisher, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - The Two Reformations, draft, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - The Two Reformations, draft-not for publication, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - The Two Reformations, catalogs, Yale University Press, circa 2002 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - The Two Reformations, review articles, 2002-2005 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - The Two Reformations, German rights, publishers, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - The Reformation: From Last Days to the Beginning of the New World, posthumous essays, Weinstein, draft, circa 2002 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - The Reformation: From Last Days to the Beginning of the New World, German alternate draft, circa 2002 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - John Calvin and the Reformation of the Refugees, draft, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Calvin, Peter Dykema, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Vatican II Materials, 1958-1979; Series VI
  Materials related to The Second Vatican Council (Vatican II). Predominately typed notes on Dutch Documentation Center (D0-C) letterhead containing Vatican II proceedings and supplementary materials organized by sections numbered 2-209. Also some clippings, news bulletins, publications and Oberman’s Vatican Passport.
  - HAO’s Vatican passport, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - D0-C, Vatican II, typed notes, No. 2-37, 1962-1965 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - D0-C, Vatican II, typed notes, No. 40-64, 1962-1965 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - D0-C, Vatican II, typed notes, No. 65-75, 1962-1965 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - D0-C, Vatican II, typed notes, No. 76-88, 1962-1965 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - D0-C, Vatican II, typed notes, No. 91-105, 1962-1965 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - D0-C, Vatican II, typed notes, No. 106-134, 1962-1965 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - D0-C, Vatican II, typed notes, No. 135-149, 1962-1965 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - D0-C, Vatican II, typed notes, No. 150-159, 1962-1965 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - D0-C, Vatican II, typed notes, No. 211-230, 1962-1965 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - D0-C, Vatican II, typed notes, No. 161-197, 1962-1965 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - D0-C, Vatican II, typed notes, No. 201-209, 1962-1965 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - D0-C, Vatican II, typed notes, Supplements, 1962-1965 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Vatican II, News Bulletin, No. 39-41, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - The Ecumenist, journal, 1965, 1966, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Vatican II, newspaper clippings, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Vatican II, photocopies, newspaper clippings, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Publications, 1958-1961 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Personal Files, Family and Colleague Correspondence, 1950-2016; Series VII
  - Journals, personal notes, 1950-1954; Subseries 1
    - HAO, journals, personal notes, 1950, 1954, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - HAO, journals, personal notes, 1952, 1954, undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - HAO, journals, personal notes, circa 1950 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - HAO, journals, personal notes (continued), circa 1950 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Personal Files (home office) and Family Correspondence, 1949-2016; Subseries 2
    Includes materials found in Oberman’s home office after his death including project files, publicity and clippings and personal effects. Contains obituaries and personal and family correspondence related to Oberman’s illness. Correspondence related to unfinished academic works with editor, publishers and colleagues.
    - Driver’s license, Indonesia, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Credos, six principles of teaching philosophy (developed by HAO), undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Awards/Honors, 1949-2001 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Berfungsangelegenheiten [Appeals], move from Harvard to Tubingen, 1965-1967 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Notes found in home office postmortem, 1980-2000 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Clippings, 1940s-1960s (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Clippings, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Clippings, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Clippings, Oberman with his families painting of Luther, Arizona Daily Star, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Clippings, 1984-1996 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Clippings, 1980-2000 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Clippings, photocopies, 1963-1996 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Master Activities List, 1982-2000 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Reviews of HAO’s work, 1981-2005 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Reviews of HAO’s work (continued), 1981-2005 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Reviews of HAO’s work, newspaper, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Reviews of HAO’s work, newspaper, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Reviews of HAO’s work, 1983-1990 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Review’s, newspaper, 1977-1982 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Publicity, 1962, 1985-2000 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Publicity, 1986-1996 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Directory listings/biographical entries, 1987-2001 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Photographs, Arizona Daily Star, 2 prints, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Family history, 1989-2005 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Permissions granted by HAO, 1991-2000 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Invitations, declined, 1991-2001 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Heineken Prize, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Koninklijke Nederlandse Akademie van Wetenschappen, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Rechtzaak Tegen Van Keulen, 1994-2000 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Holten/Ekeby, legal files, land sale, 1973-1992 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Ekeby, Natuurschoon, [Nature Preserve, Netherlands], 1993-2000 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Holten, Rabobank materials, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Ombouw, Ekeby, Toetie Oberman/Van Zon B. V., 1998-2001 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Personal and family correspondence, 1961-2000 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Dear friends letter and list (sharing news of illness), 2001 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Responses to news of illness, 2001-2006 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Funeral service, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Obituaries/family and personal correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Obituaries, newspaper, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Susan Karant-Nunn and University of Arizona correspondence, 2000-2016 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Thomas A. Brady, Jr. Correspondence, 1971-2003; Subseries 3
    Correspondence collected by Thomas A. Brady, Jr., History Professor at Stanford University and family friend. Includes professional correspondence from Oberman as Brady’s editor on behalf of Brill, and personal correspondence with Oberman and with family members after his death. Includes correspondence from Louise Betterton, staff member of the Department of Late Medieval and Reformation Studies at the University of Arizona.
    - Thomas A. Brady, Jr., correspondence, 1971-1976 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Thomas A. Brady, Jr., correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Thomas A. Brady, Jr., correspondence, 1981-1985 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Thomas A. Brady, Jr., correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Thomas A. Brady, Jr., correspondence, 1991-1999 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Thomas A. Brady, Jr., correspondence, 1998-2003 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Thomas A. Brady, Jr., correspondence, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Publications, 1958-2005; Series VIII
  Articles and offprints authored by Oberman, reviews of his work and a small collection of publications and clippings authored by others (some signed with a personal note). Organized chronologically.
  - Publications, HAO, 1958-1961 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Publications, HAO (continued), 1958-1961 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Publications, HAO, 1962-1965 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Publications, HAO (continued), 1962-1965 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Publications, HAO, 1966-1968 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Publications, HAO (continued), 1966-1968 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Publications, HAO (continued), 1966-1968 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Publications, HAO, 1969-1973 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Publications, HAO (continued), 1969-1973 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Publications, HAO, 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Publications, HAO (continued), 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Publications, HAO/Evangelische Kommentare, 1975-1978 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Publications, HAO, 1977-1981 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Publications, HAO (continued), 1977-1981 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Publications, HAO, 1982-1985 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Publications, HAO (continued), 1982-1985 (Box 27, Folder 7)